## Sam Bindloss

#### **Curriculum Vitae**

**DOB:** 19<sup>th</sup> May 1996

Email: Sam.bindloss@hotmail.com

**Phone:** 07469204884

**Address:** 9a Mauldeth Road, Manchester, M20 4NE

## **Personal Summary**

I am currently a student at Manchester Metropolitan University studying Website Development. I am a responsible, hardworking and dedicated individual who sets his aims high and will consistently work towards any given goal to the best of my ability. I also consider myself to be a sociable and confident person and believe I have gained these traits through my 4 years of experience in retail.

# **Key Attributes/Skills**

- Known coding languages HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Ajax and Json.
- Understand the full process of creating a website and have the ability to do this individually as well as part of a team.
- Managerial skills led two groups at University to successful projects.
- Interpersonal skills Ability to communicate with people at all levels
- Positive attitude Always approach the day with an upbeat mind-set
- Organisational skills Developed through academic studies
- Computer literate Effective use of Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, Excel
- Responsible Entrusted with opening and closing a store (Key holder)
- Helpful and friendly member within the team

#### **Education**

Currently studying towards a degree in (BSC) Website Development at Manchester Metropolitan University (Predicted 1<sup>st</sup>).

Triple Distinction Star (D\*D\*D\*) in ICT BTEC Extended Diploma during my time in 6<sup>th</sup> form at Blessed George Napier, Banbury.

11 GCSE's from grades A – C including Maths, Science and English.

### **Employment**



### June 2013 - July 2016

Key holder from November 2015 – July 2016 Sales assistant from June 2013 – November 2015

- Entrusted in opening and closing the store on busy days.
- Responsible in being acting manager of the store during long periods throughout the day.
- Delegation of fellow employees to carry out tasks that need to be finished before a certain time.
- Hardworking, honest and loyal member of the team.
- Consistent and strong customer service at all times.
- Quick in helping customers find what they are looking for and knowledgeable on stock to help drive large sales.
- Experience within the stock room.



June 2012 - January 2013

First job Started soon after my 16<sup>th</sup> birthday

- Started to become increasingly mature and confident as a person.
- Basic fundamentals learnt such as time keeping and presentation.
- Consistent and strong customer service at all times.
- Quick in helping customers find what they are looking for and knowledgeable on stock to help drive large sales.
- Experience within the stock room.

#### References

Stephen Mclinden (Fred Perry store manager) - Phone: 07824386519 Lucy Horseman (Former supervisor) — Phone: 07530418804